dd4.com 2015-03-21

# Security & Privacy Policy - DD4.com - Global Online Shopping for Fashions, Home & Garden, Electronics, Wedding Apparel

**Welcome to DD4, your reliable online marketplace.**

The web site identified by the uniform resource locator www.DD4.com (“DD4”) is provided by Shenzhen Dindin E-commerce Co., Ltd (“Dindin”) as a service to our customers. This Security and Privacy Policy is entered into between you as a registered user of DD4 (“Registered User”) and Dindin.

The security of your personal information is very important to us and we value your trust highly. We will not sell or loan your personal information to a third party under any circumstances. We will work hard to protect the security and privacy of any personal information you provide to us and will only use such information as we have described herein.

By your use and access of DD4, you accept this Security and Privacy Policy.

**What personal information do we collect?**

You may choose to use or access DD4 without revealing any personal and transactional information about yourself, but you will need to register and create an account in order to make a purchase or take advantage of certain features and functions. If you provide us with your information, you consent to the transfer and storage of the information on our server located in the People’s Republic of China (the “P.R.C.”).

As set forth in more detail below, Dindin collects personal information that you provide when using DD4. This information includes your first and last name, email address, a password and other information required when you create your DD4 account or when you participate in or conduct surveys and contests via DD4, email, or other media of DD4. In order to protect your confidentiality and verify your identity, we may ask you to confirm your personal information when you contact our Customer Service Department.

In addition to the personal information we may collect and process during registration and any surveys, we also collect, store and process the following information about our users:

1\. Purchase Information

When you make a purchase from DD4, we collect your name and payment method information. When you create an account at DD4, you can choose to save your billing information in “My DD4.” You can also save one or more shipping addresses in your DD4 Address Book.

2\. Services Account Information

We collect personal information from users who wish to use any of the DD4 services, including but not limited to, DD4’s Transaction Platform. In order to use these services you must provide your email address and password or create an account at DD4.

3\. Cookies and Other Computer Information

When you visit DD4, you will be assigned a permanent “cookie” (a small text file) to be stored on your computer’s hard drive. The purpose of the cookie is to identify you when you visit DD4 so that we can enhance and customize your online purchasing experience.

You can choose to browse on DD4 without cookies, but without these identifier files you will not be able to complete a purchase or take advantage of certain features of DD4. These features include storing your shopping cart for later use and providing a more personalized future shopping experience. Each browser is different, so check the “Help” menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.

We also collect certain technical information from your computer each time you request a page during a visit to DD4. This information may include your Internet Protocol (IP) address, your computer’s operating system, browser type and the address of a referring web site, if any. We collect this information to enhance the quality of your experience during your visit to DD4 and will not sell or loan this information to any third parties.

We also contract with third parties to provide us with data collection and reporting services regarding our customers’ activities on DD4 and to track and measure the performance of our marketing efforts. These third parties may use cookies and may receive anonymous information about your browsing and buying activity on DD4. None of your personally identifiable information (such as your name, address, email address, etc.) will be received by or shared with these third parties.

4\. Publishing Information

When you submit any information on DD4 during your use or access, including, but not limited to, information on the rating system, or product catalog, you are deemed to have given your permission to DD4 to publish such information, and Dindin and DD4 hereby enjoy an irrevocable, perpetual, worldwide and royalty-free, sub-licensable license to use all information provided by such user to exercise the copyright, compilation, database and publicity rights any user has in such material or information, in any media form.

**How we use your personal information?**

We do not sell, loan, trade or exchange any user’s personal information without such user’s consent. The information we collect on DD4 may be used to enhance your shopping experience in the following ways:

·       Deliver merchandise and services that you purchase online;

·       Register you as a member of DD4;

·       Prevent fraud;

·       Confirm your orders;

·       Resolve disputes and prevent prohibited and illegal activities;

·       Enforce our Terms of Use and related agreements;

·       Respond to your customer-service inquiries or requests;

·       Communicate great values and featured items to you;

·       Find and stock the products you want; and

·       Customize, measure and improve our services and your purchase experience.

**When and with whom can we share your personal information?**

We do not sell or loan your personal information to any third parties under any circumstances. We will share your personal customer information only with our agents, representatives, service providers, and contractors for limited purposes, including, but not limited to, fulfilling customer orders, offering certain products and services in connection with DD4, communicating to customers, providing customer service, storing, sharing and retrieving customers’ photo images in our Photo Center, enhancing and improving clients’ purchase experience, enabling access to our partners’ web sites, providing a personalized purchase experience and preventing fraud and completing payment method processing.

Aside from the purposes described above, we will not share your personal information with any other third parties unless we have your express permission or there are special circumstances, such as when DD4 is required by the government, law enforcement body, obligee whose legitimate right has been injured, subpoena or other legal document to share such information, or if we believe it to be reasonably necessary to protect the safety of any person; to address fraud, security or technical issues; or to protect DD4’s rights or property. We may also share aggregated demographic and statistical information with our partners. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

**How can you control the use of your personal information?**

You can modify or delete your personal information at any time. Simply go to My DD4. Log in with your ID and password, then edit or delete your personal information at your discretion.

**How can we protect the security of your personal information?**

Your personal information is protected by the password you created when you created an account on DD4 (or another password you chose after changing a previous password). Please keep this password confidential. No Customer Service Associate or any other representative of DD4 will ever ask you for your password. The confidentiality of your password is yours to protect. You may change it at anytime by going to My DD4. Log in with your email address and password, then click “Change Name, Email & Password” and enter a new password.

Minors

DD4 does not intentionally collect personal information about minors or other persons without full civil conduct capacity, but based on the properties of Internet, there is no way for DD4 and DD4 to distinguish the age or capacity of the users. By accepting this Agreement through your use or access of DD4, you certify that you are a person over 18 years old with full capacity and ability to form a legally binding contract in the jurisdiction in which you are resident or in which you are entering into this Agreement. If you do not agree to (or cannot comply with) any of the terms of this Agreement, do not use DD4.

Meanwhile, if a minor or other person does not have full civil conduct capacity and has provided personal information to us without the proper consent of their parent or legal guardian, such parent or legal guardian should contact us to remove such personal information.

Security

Your information is stored on our servers located in the P.R.C, and we adopt lots of tools, means and technologies to protect them against unauthorized access, use and disclosure. For instance, we use a technology called Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), which encrypts (or encodes) sensitive information before it is sent over the Internet. However, we are limited in our efforts by the technologies currently available, and no data transmission or storage over Internet can be guaranteed to be perfectly safe. Therefore, although we work very hard to protect your information and privacy, we do not promise or guarantee that your information will always be private and safe.

General

We realize that making purchases on DD4, or any other web site, requires trust on your part. We value your trust very highly and pledge to you, our clients, which we will work hard to protect the security and privacy of any personal information you provide to us and that your personal information will only be used as set forth in this Policy. This includes your name, address, phone number, email address or checking account information, in addition to any other personal information that can be linked to you, personally.

DD4 may provide links to certain third party web sites. This Security and Privacy Policy applies only to activities conducted and personal information collected on DD4. Other web sites may have their own policies regarding privacy and security. We encourage you to review the privacy policies on these sites before you use and access them. You are solely responsible for your use and access of other web sites.

DD4 will obtain your consent before allowing the download of any software from DD4, and DD4 will not automatically download any software to your computer system. Once you consent to the initial download of any software, you may receive automatic updates or patches pertaining to such software. You understand and agree that any material, including but not limited to downloaded software, required or automated updates, modifications, reinstallations, or software otherwise obtained through the use of DD4 is done at your own discretion and risk and that you will be solely responsible for any damages to your computer system or loss of data that may result from any such material.

DD4 reserves the right to update or modify this Security and Privacy Policy at any time without prior notice to you. The most current version of the Policy will govern DD4’s use of the information and will always be at www.dd4.com. If DD4 makes a change that, in DD4’s sole discretion, is material, DD4 will notify you via e-mail to the email address associated with your account. Your use of DD4 following any such change constitutes your unconditional agreement to follow and be bound by the Security and Privacy Policy as amended.

DD4 may transfer this Policy and all or part of its rights, obligations and interests to any party or entity in its sole discretion; however, a User may not assign its rights, obligations and interests under this Policy to any party or entity.

Terms which have not been defined or stipulated in this policy shall be interpreted in accordance with the definition(s) or provision(s) of the Terms of Use of DD4.
